# **Bing Hu**

Email: binghucnsty@gmail.com

Phone: +8615712309691

#### Profile:

As a seasoned and passionate Fullstack Engineer, I bring a wealth of experience, responsibility, and expertise to the table.

My top priority has always been to deliver business value and prioritize the customer's perspective, and I thrive in team environments where I can collaborate with both colleagues and clients.

Over the past 12 years, I have successfully implemented a multitude of customer requirements, adding substantial value to businesses. In recent years, my ability to work as a dedicated remote team member has allowed me to take on projects across different time zones.

I am eager to continue contributing my skills and experience to drive innovation and growth in this exciting field.

#### General stack is

- Golang
- Node.js
- Laravel
- Java/J2EE
- Python/Django/FastAPI
- React/React-Native
- Vue 2/3
- Angular
- Elixir

### Languages:

English, Chinese

### **Education:**

2006 – 2010 Beijing Institute of Technology, Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

# **Employment History:**

# ShengTianYang, China

Web/Mobile Developer

2010-2017

- Passed Java/J2EE, SQL, Web programing, OOP courses
- Started as ERP system maintainer(Oracle ERP)
- Developed company administration web sites(Java, Spring)

- Designed ETL product using Java and led small team to implement the product for 1 years.
- Led the development of web based ERP system and delivered successfully to client.(React.js, Golang, MongoDB)
- Led the development of SDADA product and delivered successfully to client(C++, Postgres)

# **Neusis, United States(Remote, Part Time)**

Web/Mobile Developer

 Delivered innovative web-based solutions that increased efficiency and streamline processes for clients, utilizing React.js, Vue.js, and Angular 1/2.

- Designed and launched mobile apps that improved user experience and engagement, using React Native.
- Built robust and scalable backend systems, integrating Restful/GraphQL APIs and third-party APIs, to enhance functionality and support business growth.(Golang, Node.js)
- Led the development of customized delivery service. (Node.js, Angular)
- Migrated crypto currency wallet service backend from Node.js to Go.(Node.js, Go)

### Clarus R&D, USA (Remote, Full Time)

Full stack engineer 2018-2020

- Designed and executed business logic, backend APIs, and security features for a ticket Tax credit service, resulting in improved security and reliability. (Golang, React.is)
- Developed and conducted comprehensive testing to ensure high-quality delivery of backend logic and React components.
- Participated to migrate overall platform from Golang/React to Elixir/Phonex.

# Room-Res, Australia(Remote, Full Time)

S/W Architect/Engineer

2020-2022

- Led the development of a highly successful hotel/flight reservation system that exceeded customer expectations and drove growth.(Golang, React)
- Migrated legacy Laravel backend to Golang.
- Integrated 20+ provider APIs using Rest, SOAP and graphQL.
- Developed/maintained Java Spring based CRM service.

2015-2018